-100 years ago,
there was a guy that converted
his stomach into an aquarium.
Yeah. Where he could
store live creatures.
And then he could bring them up
at will.
[ Audience groans ]
-[ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
I never heard that story.
I...
[ Laughter ]
I mean, if...
[ Audience "ohhs" ]
...if it was possible...
-No, no, no. No, no, no.
-...it would...
it would kind of...
-Oh, no.
-If it was possible...
[ Laughter ]
[ Audience "ohhs" ]
-No!
-Oh, n--
-Oh, no.
-Oh!
[ Audience screaming ]
No!
-Yo!
Oh, my God!
[ Applause ]
-David Blaine, everybody!
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Let's show them.
-It's real.
It's a real frog.
That is a real frog.
-Well...
-Oh, my gosh.
-I got to --
Guys, come over here.
No, no. I want you
to see that it's real.
Also, I'm gonna put him
back where he came from.
-Aaaahh!
[ Audience screaming ]
-Thank you, guys.
♪♪
-What are you doing with us,
me and The Roots tonight?
What's happening?
What has already happened?
Something already
must have happened.
-No, no, no, no. Simple.
No, no.
Simple, simple. Simple, simple.
We'll just do simple.
-Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
[ Laughs ]
-Just cards, you know?
-Okay. Just cards.
That's it.
Simple stuff.
-Maybe I'll try -- Which one
of you guys plays poker
a little bit?
-I do.
-Yeah?
You want to help with this?
-Sure.
-[ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
Come on, man.
-Actually, you know what?
You'll oversee it
to make sure I don't cheat.
You can see the cards
are all mixed.
Jimmy, in poker, there's usually
about five cards.
-Mm-hmm.
-Take, like, five cards.
A little group.
Like a poker hand.
-Yeah.
-Is that five? Good.
Don't let anybody see them.
Just you. Good.
-Uh-huh.
-And, Jimmy, hold them up
so only you could see it.
Like that.
Only you can see.
-Good.
-Yeah.
-And, Jimmy...
Think of -- Jimmy...
[ Laughter ]
Think any one
of those cards.
Think of any one of those cards.
-That one's too obvious.
This is...
Oh, man.
Alright, I'm thinking of it.
And, Jimmy, look at me.
Good.
-Oh, my gosh.
I'm freaking me out, man.
-Jimmy, put the cards behind
your back.
And, Jimmy, mix them.
-[ Laughing ] Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
I'm freaking out, man.
-No.
[ Laughter ]
-Whoo-hoo!
-Now, Jimmy, I want you to look
at the five cards again.
Look at all of your cards.
Don't let anybody see them.
Just you. Look at all of them.
Just you see them.
Good. Now, Jimmy, I want you to
focus on every other card
except for your card.
-Okay.
-Now, see, what's funny
is when I say that, it makes him
just focus on his card.
-[ Laughs ] That is true.
Okay.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-Jimmy, repeat after me.
-Yes.
-Say "Ace, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, Jack, Queen, King.
Go ahead.
-"Ace, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, Jack, Queen, King.
-Good. Clubs, hearts,
spades, diamonds.
-Clubs, hearts, spades,
diamonds.
-Get rid of the 10 of hearts.
That's not your card.
You can put it here
so everybody can see it.
The 10 of hearts.
-Oh, my gosh!
-I'm, like, freaking out.
[ Laughs ]
-And get rid of the obvious
one that you talked about --
the ace of diamonds.
Get rid of that one.
-[ Laughing ] Oh, my God!
Dude!
This is what I'm talking about,
man!
What is going on,
David Blaine?!
-Jimmy, get rid of
the 4 of spades.
Get rid of the 4 of spades.
-Holy moly, moly,
moly, moly, moly.
-And you know what?
Get rid of the other 4.
The 4 of diamonds.
And, Jimmy,
you thought of a card.
Get rid of the 4 of diamonds.
You thought of a card
before this began.
Show everybody
the 7 of hearts, your card.
[ Laughter,
cheers and applause ]
-Dude.
[ Laughs ] Dude.
I love you. This is the type
of stuff I'm talking about.
Oh, my gosh! See?
You can't just do that.
I don't know
how you just did that.
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, I don't know
how you did that.
-Should we try another one
just for the hell of it?
[ Cheers and applause ]
-What made him choose that?
-I don't know.
How many decks of cards
do you have in your house?
-On me? Just two.
-Just on you, two.
In your house?
-One in each pocket. Yeah.
In my house?
-Yeah.
-Like, a houseful.
[ Laughter ]
-A house of cards.
-So, hold on.
I put one card
in a specific location.
-Yeah.
-So one card goes
in a specific location
in the deck.
Fair enough? Okay.
-Yeah.
-Great trick.
[ Laughter ]
-Name any card in the deck.
Name any card out loud.
Say it out loud.
-9 of diamonds.
-9 of diamonds?
-Yeah.
-First or second?
It's up to you.
-Second.
-9 of diamonds, second.
I shuffled.
You saw me.
I placed one card in a position.
I put the 9 of diamonds
in the second position
in the deck.
Jimmy, open the box.
Turn it over. Go ahead.
-Gosh!
-Go ahead. Turn it over.
-Turn the box over?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Turn it and open it up.
-Okay.
-And pull out the whole deck.
And you said second, right?
-That's correct.
-So that's first.
Show me the second card.
[ Audience "ohhs" ]
-Dude!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
You're just amazing.
You are the greatest, man.
Oh, my gosh.
-Can I try one more?
-Yeah. Experiment.
Yeah. I don't know if this is
gonna work or not. Come on.
I'm checking my pockets.
I'm checking my pockets now.
-So can you guys
come even a little...
Yeah.
I want you to count out...
I want you
to count out loud for me.
We're gonna use 10 cards.
-My heart is beating.
-So let's count out loud.
-1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
-10 cards.
No more than 10.
-Mm-hmm.
-For this,
we don't care
about the number and the suit.
We only care about the actual
paper that makes the card.
10 cards, correct?
-Correct.
-Yes?
-Yes.
-Nobody's skeptical?
-Yeah, but...
-No, I'm saying
if you're skeptical,
then you do the count yourself.
Here. Look, feel it,
make sure that's one card.
No, no, here,
and then put it upside down
on the bottom,
like a real count.
-Okay. 1. 2.
-That's number 2. Right?
Good. Keep going out loud.
-3.
-And on the bottom. Yeah.
-4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
That's 10 cards.
-10.
Can you hold them against
your heart for me?
-Absolutely.
-Yeah. Good.
Just like that.
Keep your hand there.
-Oh, God.
-Just, as I go through --
And you can see
they're all different, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-As I go through,
I just want you
to just yell "stop."
It doesn't matter.
-Stop.
-Here? Look at the card.
-Yeah.
-See what it is. What number.
We only care about the numbers.
-Can I tell everybody?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-3. 3.
-It's a 3?
-Fine. It doesn't matter.
You have 10 cards.
You want three to travel
from here to there.
Three cards will move
from this to your pile.
Look. One card just shot
through there and landed.
-Yo, I felt something.
-Hold on.
[ Laughter ]
-Wait. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Let's do it again.
Card number two just traveled
through the air
and landed in his pile.
Hold on. One more.
Three cards
just traveled through the air
and landed on his pile.
What I want to do is,
you're gonna count 1,
2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Count there's
no longer 10 cards.
You're gonna have 13 cards.
Count them out loud,
right here for everybody.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9, 10.
10's the original number.
-Oh!
-How many are there?
11, 12, 13.
-Dude!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-Oh, my gosh!
He's unbelievable!
-Now, wait. You know what?
Take all 13,
hold them against
your heart for me.
-Oh, gosh.
-Yes.
Can you name
a number up to 10?
-3.
-3?
And can you name
a number up to 5?
-4.
-Okay, so 4.
-Hold on.
-3 for you and 4 for you.
-Yeah.
-I'm gonna move
three cards for you
and four cards for you
into his pile of 13
from back here.
There's three,
and there's four more.
Now there's 20 cards.
3 plus 4 -- 7.
Plus your 13.
When you pull the pile
off of your heart,
you'll notice
it's significantly bigger.
Pull it off your heart.
Does it feel bigger?
-It does.
-Oh, my God.
-See? There's
no longer 13 cards.
Count out loud for everybody.
-1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9, 10...
-11, 12, 13, 14,
15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
-Dude.
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
-Oh, man. Stop.
-I mean, no, no, no.
There's no one like that.
Your special airs
this Tuesday.
You always blow us away
with your magic.
What is the craziest thing
that you do in the show?
-There's a couple
of crazy things.
[ Laughter ]
-Are we gonna find out
right now?
-No, no, no. No, no, no, no.
-That's Tuesday night.
Yeah, yeah, we'll see it, yeah.
-Well, there is one
that I worked on
which is called
the Human Aquarium.
It's, like, one of my
favorite things.
The concept is,
a hundred years ago,
there was a guy that converted
his stomach into an aquarium.
Yeah. Where he could
store live creatures.
And then he could bring them up
at will.
[ Audience groans ]
-[ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
I never heard that story.
I...
[ Laughter ]
I mean, if...
[ Audience "ohhs" ]
...if it was possible...
-No, no, no. No, no, no.
-it would...
it would kind of...
-Oh, no.
-If it was possible...
[ Laughter ]
[ Audience "ohhs" ]
-No!
-Oh, n--
-Oh, no.
-Oh!
[ Audience screaming ]
No!
-Yo!
Oh, my God!
[ Applause ]
-David Blaine, everybody!
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Let's show them.
-It's real.
It's a real frog.
That is a real frog.
-Well...
-Oh, my gosh.
-Could I use your phone?
-Uh-huh.
[ Laughter ]
-So glad
he didn't ask me for mine.
'Cause that would've been a no.
-Yes, you can use my phone.
-I want Priyanka --
I want you
to be able to film this.
-Oh! Yes.
-And you can -- Yeah.
-Okay.
-You want me to do anything?
You want me
to turn it on or anything?
-I mean, that's how it
usually works, right?
-No, just --
No, I think we can just --
I think we can just --
-Don't use my credit card.
[ Laughter ]
-That one.
-Don't worry.
You can change your code.
[ Laughter ]
-Do you already know his code?
-Can you --
Can you hold this like this?
-Okay.
-And I'll just
record that, as well.
Good. And I might need just
to use this to see the trick.
So, do you want
to see the card trick
or the needle-and-thread trick?
[ Laughter ]
-You're already in my head.
Already, right?
Uh, the card trick.
Right? No?
-Perfect.
We'll do the needle and thread.
[ Laughter ]
-Oh, my God.
-For this,
I need exactly this length.
-What?
What are you stitching?
-Well, I need it exactly,
I'd say...
[ Light laughter ]
-Yo!
[ Laughter and applause ]
-Whew! Whew!
Okay.
[ Light laughter ]
Very cute.
-No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-Oh, my God, no.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-Oh, my God!
-Ohh!
[ Audience gasps ]
-Stop!
-Aah!
-I can't focus! I can't focus!
[ Laughter ]
I'm focusing, I'm focusing.
[ Audience shouts ]
I can't look at -- I can't --
-Aah!
-Oh, my God.
[ Audience gasps ]
-[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Laughter ]
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh...my gosh.
-Aah.
-I think that's --
-Oh, man.
-Guys, there's blood on it
and everything.
-There's blood on it.
There's blood on it.
-This is some
"Game of Thrones" stuff.
-This is insane.
[ Audience gasps, shouts ]
-David, stop!
[ Laughter ]
-Oh!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
-Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo,
yo, yo, yo, yo!
Yo, yo, yo!
Oh, my God, yo.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, for crying --
Ooh.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Oh, my gosh.
-Nah, man! No!
No! No!
-Questlove!
Questlove!
Come on, just do it.
Just do it.
Questlove, just come back.
-For what?
-Because you have to see
everything.
You have to finish the trick.
This is insane.
-Get him to do it.
-Just -- Questlove, please.
Oh, my gosh.
-Ohhhhhh!
-Oh, God, no, one more time.
No.
-David....
[ Audience gasps ]
David, what is going on, dude?
What's --
[ Laughter ]
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
How you doing, man?
No! No, no.
I really --
I don't know
if I can do it, man.
[ Laughter ]
I feel bad.
Okay.
-Aah.
-Aah!
[ Audience gasps ]
-Oh!
Oh!
[ Laughter ]
Jimmy!
Aah!
[ Audience groans ]
-Oh, my gosh, dude.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so sorry.
-Guys, there's blood on it.
-I'm so sorry.
That is insane.
-There's blood on that.
-That is unreal.
Don't smile, dude.
[ Laughter ]
I can't --
I can't unsee this, dude.
Tie it?
In a thing?
In a knot.
All right, yeah.
Make a knot?
Oh, my gosh, David.
I don't want to do this, man.
Oh, my gosh.
We should've done
the card trick.
[ Laughter ]
I'm telling you, we should've
done the card trick.
-Oh, God.
My camera skills are horrible.
-Oh, my gosh.
All right.
All right, so...
Oh, my gosh.
I can't even tie a knot.
I'm freaking out right now.
[ Laughter ]
-Aah.
-Okay.
That's a knot.
Well, thanks for coming, David.
[ Laughter ]
It's always good to see you,
and you're on tour
starting May, uh...
May 9th, in San Diego.
Do you have something?
The card trick.
Yeah, the card trick, yeah.
We should've done
the card trick, absolutely, yes.
You're gonna do that while I --
-I'm still recording, right?
I'm just check -- Yeah.
[ Laughter ]
Clarify.
-I hope that's
a normal deck of cards.
-Normal deck of cards.
Yes, yes, yes.
[ Laughter ]
I-I should check it.
Yes.
Normal.
Oh, pick one,
pick one, pick one.
[ Laughter ]
Okay.
Picked one.
Show it to everyone but not you.
You all see it?
Put it back in there?
Oh, no, hold the deck.
Oh, he saw it.
Okay.
[ Laughter ]
-Yeah, not impressive.
You ripped the card.
[ Laughter ]
Oh, I thought you were showing
me how strong you are.
Yes.
[ Laughter ]
-Okay.
And I put the rest of it
back in the deck?
On top of the deck.
Oh, I hold it.
-Yeah.
God, I feel like
I'm speaking ESL again.
[ Laughter ]
Okay.
[ Audience murmuring ]
Oh, my God! If that comes out
of where I think it is...
[ Laughter ]
-No. His -- His mouth?
Is that what you're thinking?
No, David, don't --
-I'm having a --
[ Laughter ]
-David...
No, no, no.
Dude, this dude is insane.
[ Audience gasps ]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
[ Laughter ]
Okay.
Gosh.
Tariq, you want to do this?
Here, you do this, man.
-Ugh.
-It's like surgery.
-Geez.
Aah.
-Don't cut his --
That's his lip.
Aah.
-Tariq...
-Okay. Okay.
Okay.
-Aah!
[ Audience gasps ]
Yaaah!
[ Laughter ]
-Man...
[ Audience groans ]
-Oh.
-Jimmy, you must open it
for us to see.
-Okay.
Ugh!
-Aah!
-Holy...
-No way.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-Oh, my gosh.
This is unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
-Could I just have a little
water just to clean up?
Thank you.
-Oh, wait.
Aw, man.
[ Audience gasps ]
-Oh!
-[ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
-Am I clean?
-Yeah.
-You're clean.
-No blood?
No blood.
-A little -- no.
A little blood, I mean.
-Just a little blood, I mean...
-Wow, there he goes.
[ Laughter ]
Do I go to the card now?
That was insane.
You're about to kick off
a huge tour next month.
You have 36 shows
all across North America.
What can people expect
from these shows?
[ Laughter ]
Expect to see some different --
Some different --
-Jimmy?
-Yes?
-Is my mouth empty?
[ Audience gasps ]
-No!
-Yes.
-Is there nothing...?
[ Laughter ]
-Questlove.
-No!
[ Laughter ]
[ Audience gasps ]
-Questlove.
[ Indistinct shouting ]
-Yo, man.
[ Laughter ]
-Oh.
-[ Shouts ]
[ Audience gasps ]
[ Laughter, cheers, applause ]
♪♪
-I have to throw up.
I have to throw up.
-Everybody, I think you all have
an envelope under your seats.
You do, too.
There's an envelope
under your seats.
It should be --
And it says, "Do not open."
Everybody hold that envelope up.
You all have -- Good, great.
Just rip it open, and there's
a deck of cards in the envelope.
Everybody open the box
and pour all of the cards
into your hand.
Make sure they don't spill.
And turn it face-down.
Good. The box is empty? Great.
Put the box on the floor.
You don't need it.
Turn all the cards face-down.
-Yeah.
-Hold it in your hand
just like that.
Perfect. Great.
Is everybody
holding the deck face-down?
Okay, I want everybody to just
pick up a bunch of cards.
And everybody show us --
Everybody show the card that you
cut to, so turn it over.
-Can I show it?
-Yeah, turn it over. Great.
Did you all do that,
just like Jimmy?
Leave that file face-up
and put it on top of the pile
in your hand with --
Just like that.
So, spread through the face-up
cards to the last face-up card.
Go ahead, spread through.
And you'll see
they're all different,
until you see the first
face-down card, just like Jimmy.
And put the face-up pile
on the bottom now.
Everybody
put them on the bottom.
Yeah, just like that. Perfect.
And watch they don't spill.
They're a little slippery.
Okay, so, we're going to
take five cards.
So count five cards.
One, two, three, four, five.
Yep, take five cards. Good.
Is -- Everybody has five cards?
Which is like a poker --
And leave them face-down
in your hands, everybody.
And get rid of the big pile.
Throw it on the floor,
whatever you want.
-Big cleanup here tonight.
-Great.
Okay, now choose anybody
in the audience at random.
I don't care.
Just call somebody out.
It's up to you. You choose.
-Alright, I will
say that guy over there
with the striped shirt
right there with the blond hair.
-Oh, great. Could you stand up?
-Yes.
-So, pick a number
between 1 and 5.
Say it out loud.
-4.
-4?
Everybody take the fourth card
and hide it in your pocket.
So, count, face-down,
1, 2, 3, 4.
And take the fourth card
and hide it in your pocket.
Don't let anybody see it.
Or sit on it
if you don't have pockets.
Everybody hide the card.
Everybody did that?
-Yes.
-Okay, get rid of
the other cards.
Get rid of all the other cards.
We don't need them.
Everybody drop them
on the floor.
-Floor, yeah, exactly.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it's unbelievable.
-Now, now, Jimmy --
-It's great to
see you, buddy, yeah.
-Jimmy, we brought some pins.
-Mm-hmm.
-There's pins.
Could you grab
these little pins right here?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
-Okay.
-This is going to be fun.
-What are you doing to me, bud?
-I don't know.
And -- I don't know.
Can you look at them
and make sure they're real pins?
Don't hurt yourself.
Don't, like, snap one.
-Yeah. Okay. Yeah, this is --
-Yeah? It's a real pin?
-These are pins.
-And they're sharp.
-Yes, yes.
I know, Questlove.
Don't freak out.
Yeah.
Yes, these are sharp pins.
-Can you pull one
of the pins out?
-Please don't make me
do anything to you, David.
'Cause I honestly --
I love having you on the show.
I don't like hurting you.
-And can you --
Let's see if we can do it on
your desk, actually, here.
So, I'm going to try to
stick this in.
No, you know what?
Can you hand me
the deck of cards?
Great.
So, let's do like this here.
I'm going to use the -- And you
see all the cards in the deck.
So, we'll use -- Here.
We'll use maybe the joker card
as a best card.
So, here.
We'll use this card, the joker.
-Okay.
-So, we use the joker,
and I'm going to bend it
a little more, like that,
so it'll stick.
-Okay.
-So, now I'm going to
take the pin,
and stick it right in
the card like that.
Now it'll stick.
You see that?
-Okay.
-So, the pin is definitely
sticking into the card.
Jimmy, hold your hand like this.
No, you're not going to
do anything.
Yeah, yeah, your other hand,
the right hand.
Open -- Yeah, yeah.
Open, open, open.
Good. Make it -- Yeah.
And just feel gently.
Feel it.
Is that really a sharp pin?
Gently, gently.
It's really there?
-Yes.
-It's sharp?
-Yes?
-Yes.
-Okay, good.
So, Jimmy,
what we're going to do is,
we're going to slam...
-Aah!
-...your hand down onto
the pin as hard as you can.
-Aah!
-No, no.
Please don't do this, David.
-But let me just show
you like this.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Let's do it together.
Look. One, two, three.
-I've had,
like, hand injuries, David.
Please, please. I've had --
-Hold on.
We're going to do it like this.
Look. 1, 2, 3,
and we're gonna slam,
but right in the middle.
-Aah-ha, David! No!
-We're going to go together.
Ready?
-No, please, please, please.
-One, two...
No, I'm just kidding.
-My gosh!
-Aah!
♪♪
-I can't do it. I can't.
Gosh!
-Jimmy, come back.
-You freak me out!
You're going to make me do that!
-No, no,
I wouldn't make you do that.
-Don't make me do that, please!
Oh, my gosh.
-Jimmy, before we do that --
-Yes! What?!
-Jimmy, before we do that,
you see all the cards
in the deck are different, yes?
-Yes.
-I'm going to run through
the cards,
and I want you to just try to
see one inside.
But here.
Like, I'm going to
run through like this.
It might be hard to see.
Try to see one inside
if you can.
But don't say it.
-Yes.
-You got one?
-Okay. Give me your hand again.
We're going to slam together
as hard as we can,
and you're going to slam
as hard as you can with me.
You have to trust me on this.
Ready?
On one, two...
[ Drumroll ]
By the way,
nobody should try this.
No kid should do this.
I'm a trained magician.
-Oh, my gosh.
One -- we're going to go
together...
two -- Jimmy, together.
-Aah!
Oh, my gosh.
-Jimmy, what was the card
you thought of?
-5 of hearts.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
[ Laughs ]
-But -- but wait.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
But before Jimmy did this,
you all cut the cards
and you all took a card
at random.
I think you cut,
then you thought of a --
Then you hid the card.
And you -- Can you all
pull your card out together?
And can we see what card
you all have?
♪♪
-Come on!
Ladies and gentlemen,
that is exactly
how you do it right there.
David Blaine right there!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Oh, my God.
You guys, David Blaine.
When does the show start?
-Well, hold on, Jimmy.
No, no, no.
Jimmy, so, you're okay.
There's nothing here.
But I wanted to up it
a little bit.
I brought something else.
Can you --
I brought a box of nails.
Jimmy, can you pull out
the box of nails and the bowl?
Yeah, take them out.
See, there's a bowl.
-Yes.
-Yeah, you can --
Here, I'll move this.
You can just --
Yeah, we just need the --
Yeah, just need --
Yeah, perfect.
[ Nails rattle ]
Can you check that
they're real nails, Jimmy?
-Let's go to commercial, and
then we'll figure it all out.
-We're not going anywhere.
[ Laughter ]
Dump them all into here.
Dump all the nails
into the bowl.
Can you mix them around, make
sure they're all real nails?
Check them. Mix them up.
Are they real nails?
-Oh, my gosh.
Yes, they are very sharp,
heavy, real metal nails.
-So, these are real nails.
Is that true?
-Yes.
-Are they sharp?
-Yes, they're very sharp.
-Oh, you picked one up?
Let me see that one.
Gimme. Gimme.
I'm going to bite it.
-Okay, okay.
-Yeah.
Yeah?
-Yes.
♪♪
-David -- David,
what in the world?
David Blaine
is eating nails right now.
This is insane.
This is -- this is all real.
This is crazy.
-You want some?
-No, thank you.
I don't want to eat...
How?
How...
-[ Coughs ]
How did you just...
Stop eating nails!
Stop eating -- David!
Oh, my God.
This is insane right now.
David Blaine is just eating
a bowl of nails right now.
♪♪
-[ Coughs ]
How in the --
-Wait, Jimmy.
Just...
[ Coughs ]
Just push right here for me.
Push right here, lightly.
Yeah, lightly. Go ahead.
Push lightly.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-Thank you very much
for, uh -- for --
-I feel like I still have...
[ Drumroll ]
-David, don't do this.
-No!
-No, don't do this.
Don't -- Not the --
Oh, my gosh, another nail.
Oh, my gosh. This is insane.
-It's not a nail.
Oh, it's not...
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
-What was that...